Yes, that is really how conversations with recruiters can go.
是的 与招聘人员的对话就像这样
Chris was able to communicate a lot of his elevator pitch
Chris 在简短的对话中用到了他的
in the short conversation.
电梯演讲中的很多内容
>> Talking to a stranger can be daunting but I was relaxed and confident.
和陌生人交谈的确会让人无所适从 但是我非常放松自信
I didn't recite my elevator pitch because I'd already practiced
我并没有从头到尾地背诵电梯演讲 因为我已经练习了
it multiple times and knew I wanted employers to know about me.
很多遍 知道我想向雇主突出自己的哪些方面
So it was easy to [INAUDIBLE] a conversation.
所以很容易就能将对话进行下去
Once the mood was set in the conversation,
一旦在谈话中营造了融洽的气氛
it was even easier to continue talking.
继续交谈就更加容易了
>> If we were able to continue the conversation, I may have asked him which
如果我们继续交谈 我会问到他在从事什么项目
other projects he worked on or how he became interested in education.
或者他是如何对教育产生兴趣的
I would have found out about his teaching background and
我会了解到他的教学背景
would have been really impressed that he was able to develop a new skill set, so
并对他能够在做全职工作的同时
successfully while still working full time.
成功学到一门新技能感到佩服
I would leave that conversation thinking Chris was a software engineer
结束谈话时 我会将 Chris 当成一名软件工程师
because he immediately proved it to me by talking about his web app.
因为他通过谈论他的 Web 应用很快证明了这一点
And that he was really serious about learning and
并且通过他的其他工作经验表现出
education due to his other work experiences.
对学习和教育的认真态度
He's the perfect engineering candidate for an education company like Udacity.
对于优达学城这样的教育公司 他是完美的工程师候选人
>> Using an elevator pitch to prep you for
使用电梯演讲为与招聘人员的对话做准备
conversations with recruiters is probably the best way to use them,
可以说是电梯演讲的最佳用途
since you're personally connecting with someone face to face.
因为到时候你将面对面地与对方建立个人联系
I also really recommend you use your pitch as a starting point to continue
我也非常建议你使用电梯演讲作为一个起点 继续
telling your personal narrative, so just through blogs or podcasts.
通过博客或播客讲述自己的故事
Employers actively try to find job candidates on the Internet,
如今 很多雇主会通过一些求职平台 如 LinkedIn 和 GitHub
on job focused platforms LinkedIn and GitHub and
以及非求职平台 如 Twitter 和 Medium
on non job focused platforms, Twitter and Medium.
寻找求职者
Now, I'm not actively looking for a job but
现在 虽然我并没有求职
opportunities still come to me because of a personally branded online presence.
但仍然会有一些机会找到我 因为我在网上建立了个人营销资料
>> So when you're looking for
所以在你求职时
work, putting your personal friend out there is like putting out
在网上发布个人资料就如同发出去
hundred of flyers advertising that you're great job candidate.
上百页传单 宣传你是一名优秀的求职者
Following this lesson, there's some project you can use to help
在这节课之后 你可以使用我们提供的一些项目来帮助
optimize your online networking profiles.
优化你的网上个人资料
Take advantage of them and watch opportunities start coming your way.
希望你充分利用它们 然后等待机会来敲门吧